[
  {
    "question": "(-6)(-x^2 + 7)",
    "answer": "6x^2 - 42"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4)(2x^2 - 6)",
    "answer": "8x^2 - 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7)(6x + 8)",
    "answer": "-42x - 56"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-1)(-3x^2 - 8)",
    "answer": "3x^2 + 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4)(-9x^3 + 7)",
    "answer": "36x^3 - 28"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5)(8x + 5)",
    "answer": "-40x - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6)(-x^2 - 3)",
    "answer": "6x^2 + 18"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-1)(-8x^3 + 3)",
    "answer": "8x^3 - 3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6)(-6x^4 - 6)",
    "answer": "36x^4 + 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8)(-x^4 + 3)",
    "answer": "8x^4 - 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9)(4x^3 + 4)",
    "answer": "-36x^3 - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-1)(-4x + 2)",
    "answer": "4x - 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9)(4x - 2)",
    "answer": "36x - 18"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5)(2x^4 - 5)",
    "answer": "25 - 10x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8)(-9x^3 + 4)",
    "answer": "32 - 72x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9)(x - 9)",
    "answer": "81 - 9x"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7)(2x + 9)",
    "answer": "-14x - 63"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9)(7x^2 - 2)",
    "answer": "63x^2 - 18"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-1)(x^4 + 3)",
    "answer": "-x^4 - 3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7)(2x^2 - 6)",
    "answer": "42 - 14x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8)(-6x^3 - 8)",
    "answer": "-48x^3 - 64"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5)(2x^3 - 8)",
    "answer": "10x^3 - 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5)(-3x^4 + 3)",
    "answer": "15x^4 - 15"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8)(7x^2 - 6)",
    "answer": "56x^2 - 48"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5)(5x^2 + 9)",
    "answer": "25x^2 + 45"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-1)(4x^3 - 9)",
    "answer": "9 - 4x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7)(4x + 3)",
    "answer": "-28x - 21"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9)(2x^4 - 6)",
    "answer": "18x^4 - 54"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7)(7x^2 - 9)",
    "answer": "63 - 49x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9)(8x^2 - 5)",
    "answer": "45 - 72x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3)(-2x^3 - 3)",
    "answer": "-6x^3 - 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(6)(4x^3 - 3)",
    "answer": "24x^3 - 18"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9)(-3x^2 + 7)",
    "answer": "63 - 27x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4)(-4x^3 - 1)",
    "answer": "-16x^3 - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2)(-5x^4 + 3)",
    "answer": "6 - 10x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4)(-5x^4 - 2)",
    "answer": "-20x^4 - 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5)(-6x^2 + 5)",
    "answer": "30x^2 - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9)(-4x^3 + 7)",
    "answer": "63 - 36x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9)(4x^4 + 3)",
    "answer": "36x^4 + 27"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-1)(7x^3 + 2)",
    "answer": "-7x^3 - 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4)(6x^2 - 3)",
    "answer": "12 - 24x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8)(3x^3 - 1)",
    "answer": "24x^3 - 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2)(8x - 3)",
    "answer": "16x - 6"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6)(2x^3 + 1)",
    "answer": "-12x^3 - 6"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9)(9x + 8)",
    "answer": "81x + 72"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8)(-6x + 7)",
    "answer": "56 - 48x"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8)(-4x^2 + 7)",
    "answer": "32x^2 - 56"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9)(5x^4 - 6)",
    "answer": "45x^4 - 54"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2)(3x^2 + 3)",
    "answer": "-6x^2 - 6"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4)(6x^3 + 2)",
    "answer": "24x^3 + 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2)(-9x^4 - -8y^2)",
    "answer": "-18x^4 + 16y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(7)(-3x^3 + 4y^2)",
    "answer": "-21x^3 + 28y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6)(-7x^2 + 3y)",
    "answer": "42x^2 - 18y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3)(9x^2 + 2y)",
    "answer": "27x^2 + 6y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6)(-6x^4 - 7y^3)",
    "answer": "36x^4 + 42y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7)(-5x^2 + 6y^2)",
    "answer": "35x^2 - 42y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5)(4x - 4y^3)",
    "answer": "20x - 20y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(6)(x^3 - 8y^4)",
    "answer": "6x^3 - 48y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5)(2x^4 + y^4)",
    "answer": "-10x^4 - 5y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(7)(-7x^4 + -8y^2)",
    "answer": "-49x^4 - 56y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9)(-6x - 5y^4)",
    "answer": "-54x - 45y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9)(3x^2 + -4y^3)",
    "answer": "27x^2 - 36y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4)(6x^2 - 5y^2)",
    "answer": "24x^2 - 20y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2)(3x^3 - -2y^4)",
    "answer": "-6x^3 - 4y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4)(8x^2 - -2y^3)",
    "answer": "32x^2 + 8y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-1)(-7x^2 - -9y^4)",
    "answer": "7x^2 - 9y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-1)(-8x - -8y^2)",
    "answer": "8x - 8y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4)(-2x^4 + -5y^3)",
    "answer": "8x^4 + 20y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5)(5x^4 - -8y^4)",
    "answer": "-25x^4 - 40y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6)(8x^2 - -5y^3)",
    "answer": "-48x^2 - 30y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5)(-9x + 8y^3)",
    "answer": "-45x + 40y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6)(4x^2 + -2y^3)",
    "answer": "-24x^2 + 12y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3)(-2x^3 - 9y)",
    "answer": "6x^3 + 27y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8)(-9x^3 - 9y^3)",
    "answer": "-72x^3 - 72y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9)(2x^4 + 8y^2)",
    "answer": "-18x^4 - 72y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5)(3x - 6y^3)",
    "answer": "15x - 30y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8)(6x - -8y^3)",
    "answer": "48x + 64y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5)(-6x^4 - 6y^3)",
    "answer": "-30x^4 - 30y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4)(6x^2 + 2y^3)",
    "answer": "24x^2 + 8y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5)(9x^2 - 3y^2)",
    "answer": "45x^2 - 15y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8)(-2x + -y^4)",
    "answer": "-16x - 8y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6)(7x^2 + -4y)",
    "answer": "-42x^2 + 24y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5)(-2x^2 - -5y^2)",
    "answer": "-10x^2 + 25y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(6)(-7x^3 + -2y^4)",
    "answer": "-42x^3 - 12y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4)(2x^2 + 4y^4)",
    "answer": "-8x^2 - 16y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6)(-5x^2 - 8y)",
    "answer": "30x^2 + 48y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9)(-4x^2 - 4y^2)",
    "answer": "36x^2 + 36y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7)(6x^3 + -2y^2)",
    "answer": "-42x^3 + 14y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-1)(2x^4 - 7y)",
    "answer": "-2x^4 + 7y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2)(4x - -2y)",
    "answer": "-8x - 4y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9)(8x^4 + 6y^2)",
    "answer": "72x^4 + 54y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5)(9x^4 - 3y)",
    "answer": "45x^4 - 15y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3)(x + -2y^2)",
    "answer": "-3x + 6y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(6)(-5x^3 + -y)",
    "answer": "-30x^3 - 6y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6)(4x^4 + -6y^2)",
    "answer": "-24x^4 + 36y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(6)(4x^4 - 3y^2)",
    "answer": "24x^4 - 18y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9)(9x^3 + -8y^3)",
    "answer": "81x^3 - 72y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8)(-2x^2 - 6y^3)",
    "answer": "16x^2 + 48y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2)(9x^4 - -6y^3)",
    "answer": "-18x^4 - 12y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7)(8x^3 - -2y^3)",
    "answer": "-56x^3 - 14y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3x^3)(5x + 5)",
    "answer": "-15x^4 - 15x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9x)(x^4 + 3)",
    "answer": "-9x^5 - 27x"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4x^2)(-x^3 + 9)",
    "answer": "-4x^5 + 36x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(6x^3)(5x - 5)",
    "answer": "30x^4 - 30x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4x^4)(4x^4 - 3)",
    "answer": "-16x^8 + 12x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5x^2)(-x^3 + 4)",
    "answer": "-5x^5 + 20x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3x)(8x^3 - 3)",
    "answer": "-24x^4 + 9x"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-x^2)(-7x^2 - 7)",
    "answer": "7x^4 + 7x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-x)(8x^2 + 6)",
    "answer": "-8x^3 - 6x"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8x^4)(-8x^3 + 4)",
    "answer": "64x^7 - 32x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3x^3)(x^3 - 8)",
    "answer": "3x^6 - 24x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3x^2)(-9x^2 + 8)",
    "answer": "-27x^4 + 24x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(6x^3)(6x - 4)",
    "answer": "36x^4 - 24x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5x^2)(5x^4 - 6)",
    "answer": "-25x^6 + 30x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9x^4)(-6x^2 - 8)",
    "answer": "-54x^6 - 72x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4x^4)(3x^2 - 7)",
    "answer": "12x^6 - 28x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4x^2)(2x^3 - 5)",
    "answer": "-8x^5 + 20x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-x)(9x^4 - 2)",
    "answer": "-9x^5 + 2x"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4x^4)(-9x^4 - 7)",
    "answer": "36x^8 + 28x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(6x^2)(-3x + 5)",
    "answer": "-18x^3 + 30x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4x)(8x^4 - 2)",
    "answer": "-32x^5 + 8x"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-x^3)(8x^2 - 8)",
    "answer": "-8x^5 + 8x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4x^4)(-9x - 9)",
    "answer": "36x^5 + 36x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7x^3)(-5x - 1)",
    "answer": "35x^4 + 7x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(7x)(4x^3 - 8)",
    "answer": "28x^4 - 56x"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-x)(4x + 5)",
    "answer": "-4x^2 - 5x"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6x)(4x^2 + 1)",
    "answer": "-24x^3 - 6x"
  },
  {
    "question": "(7x)(6x - 1)",
    "answer": "42x^2 - 7x"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2x^2)(-6x - 1)",
    "answer": "-12x^3 - 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2x^4)(-4x^3 + 8)",
    "answer": "8x^7 - 16x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8x^2)(-9x^3 + 8)",
    "answer": "-72x^5 + 64x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9x^3)(-9x + 5)",
    "answer": "81x^4 - 45x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4x)(2x^2 - 3)",
    "answer": "-8x^3 + 12x"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6x^4)(-9x^4 - 7)",
    "answer": "54x^8 + 42x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4x^2)(-2x + 2)",
    "answer": "-8x^3 + 8x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9x^3)(-2x + 9)",
    "answer": "18x^4 - 81x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x^4)(3x^2 - 7)",
    "answer": "3x^6 - 7x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4x^2)(2x^2 + 9)",
    "answer": "-8x^4 - 36x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x^3)(-9x^2 + 7)",
    "answer": "-9x^5 + 7x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4x^2)(4x^4 + 9)",
    "answer": "-16x^6 - 36x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6x^2)(5x^4 - 7)",
    "answer": "-30x^6 + 42x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8x^2)(3x + 3)",
    "answer": "-24x^3 - 24x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-x^4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "-x^5 - 5x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3x^4)(-7x^4 - 8)",
    "answer": "21x^8 + 24x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7x)(-5x^4 - 3)",
    "answer": "35x^5 + 21x"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4x^3)(7x^2 - 5)",
    "answer": "-28x^5 + 20x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x^2)(4x^4 + 2)",
    "answer": "4x^6 + 2x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4x^2)(3x^3 - 1)",
    "answer": "12x^5 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-x^4)(-9x + 2)",
    "answer": "9x^5 - 2x^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6x^3)(4x^3 - 1)",
    "answer": "-24x^6 + 6x^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5x^3)(3x^2 - 4y^2)",
    "answer": "15x^5 - 20x^3y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7x^3)(-9x^4 + 3y^4)",
    "answer": "63x^7 - 21x^3y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8x^3)(8x^3 - 2y^4)",
    "answer": "64x^6 - 16x^3y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2x^3)(-4x^2 - -y^3)",
    "answer": "-8x^5 + 2x^3y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4x^2)(-9x - -y^4)",
    "answer": "-36x^3 + 4x^2y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8x^2)(-5x^2 - -7y)",
    "answer": "40x^4 - 56x^2y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3x^4)(-2x^2 + 3y)",
    "answer": "-6x^6 + 9x^4y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3x^2)(-5x^3 + y^4)",
    "answer": "15x^5 - 3x^2y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5x^4)(-6x + -y)",
    "answer": "-30x^5 - 5x^4y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(6x^4)(2x^2 - -5y)",
    "answer": "12x^6 + 30x^4y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4x^4)(2x^4 - -6y^4)",
    "answer": "8x^8 + 24x^4y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5x)(8x^3 + -y^2)",
    "answer": "-40x^4 + 5xy^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4x^3)(4x - -2y^3)",
    "answer": "16x^4 + 8x^3y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8x^4)(8x - 6y^3)",
    "answer": "-64x^5 + 48x^4y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9x)(2x + 4y^4)",
    "answer": "-18x^2 - 36xy^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7x^4)(-4x^4 - -8y^4)",
    "answer": "28x^8 - 56x^4y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(6x^2)(8x^4 - -5y)",
    "answer": "48x^6 + 30x^2y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x^2)(-6x + 8y^3)",
    "answer": "-6x^3 + 8x^2y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6x^4)(6x^3 - -6y^4)",
    "answer": "-36x^7 - 36x^4y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3x^3)(-x + 5y)",
    "answer": "3x^4 - 15x^3y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2x^3)(2x^2 - -9y^4)",
    "answer": "-4x^5 - 18x^3y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4x^4)(-8x^2 - -y^3)",
    "answer": "32x^6 - 4x^4y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2x)(-x^3 + -2y^3)",
    "answer": "2x^4 + 4xy^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8x^4)(-8x^3 + 6y)",
    "answer": "-64x^7 + 48x^4y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-x^3)(-2x - -2y^4)",
    "answer": "2x^4 - 2x^3y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-x^3)(7x^2 + 6y^3)",
    "answer": "-7x^5 - 6x^3y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6x)(7x^2 - 5y^2)",
    "answer": "-42x^3 + 30xy^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x^3)(-4x^3 + 9y^3)",
    "answer": "-4x^6 + 9x^3y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8x)(-2x^4 + 3y^3)",
    "answer": "16x^5 - 24xy^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4x^3)(-4x^3 - -3y)",
    "answer": "16x^6 - 12x^3y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9x^4)(-4x^4 - 9y^4)",
    "answer": "-36x^8 - 81x^4y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2x^2)(-4x^4 + -4y^2)",
    "answer": "-8x^6 - 8x^2y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5x^4)(4x^2 - y^4)",
    "answer": "-20x^6 + 5x^4y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x^2)(x^4 + 8y)",
    "answer": "x^6 + 8x^2y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(6x^2)(-5x^2 - 8y^3)",
    "answer": "-30x^4 - 48x^2y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x^3)(-9x^2 + 9y^3)",
    "answer": "-9x^5 + 9x^3y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2x^4)(-x^4 + 4y^3)",
    "answer": "-2x^8 + 8x^4y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7x^2)(-6x^3 - -3y)",
    "answer": "42x^5 - 21x^2y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6x)(-7x^4 + 9y^3)",
    "answer": "42x^5 - 54xy^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7x)(8x^2 - -3y)",
    "answer": "-56x^3 - 21xy"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3x^3)(-8x^2 + 8y)",
    "answer": "-24x^5 + 24x^3y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9x^2)(-4x^3 + 4y)",
    "answer": "-36x^5 + 36x^2y"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6x^4)(2x^2 - -6y^3)",
    "answer": "-12x^6 - 36x^4y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-x^2)(5x^2 - 5y^4)",
    "answer": "-5x^4 + 5x^2y^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4x)(9x^4 - -y^4)",
    "answer": "36x^5 + 4xy^4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-x)(-3x^2 + -4y^2)",
    "answer": "3x^3 + 4xy^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8x^4)(-9x^3 + -2y^3)",
    "answer": "72x^7 + 16x^4y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2x^2)(-2x^4 - -2y^3)",
    "answer": "-4x^6 + 4x^2y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3x^2)(9x^3 + -4y^3)",
    "answer": "27x^5 - 12x^2y^3"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4x^2)(-4x^2 - -2y^3)",
    "answer": "16x^4 - 8x^2y^3"
  }
]